This is your Coordinator Dashboard,
the control room for keeping
the build-out pipeline moving. Your
job is to triage incoming
work, reassign when someone's blocked,
and clear bottlenecks before they
snowball. Start with Suggested Tasks.
Five cards are ready to
be picked up, and each
one shows the size, the
priority, and the deadline at
a glance. When a card
looks right for the team,
the Pick Up button claims
it in a single click
and moves it into Active
Task. Over in the sidebar,
your Coordinator Queue is the
number that matters most: nine
items are waiting on your
call right now, decisions only
you can make. The status
counters across the top give
you the team pulse, including
twenty-one tasks On Hold that
probably need a nudge. Below
that, Review Submissions is sitting
on five drafts already waiting
for sign-off, so designers don't
stall on you. Use Active
Task, My Backlog, Team Board,
and Notifications in the sidebar
to switch contexts as the
day evolves. From this one
screen you can triage, reassign,
unblock, and approve without ever
losing the thread.