Welcome to your Coordinator dashboard.
Suggested Tasks lists fresh work
you can claim — five
cards waiting on your call
right now. Click Pick Up
on any card to claim
it instantly — size, priority
and deadline shown. Your Coordinator
Queue shows nine items needing
triage decisions before they reach
the design team. Review Submissions
holds five drafts already waiting
on your approval before work
moves forward downstream. The status
strip surfaces approved, on hold,
and active counts so you
spot bottlenecks fast. Team Board
and Block Health track who
is loaded right now. From
here you triage, unblock, and
keep flowing.